binary.com 2011-12-26

# Binary Systems - Privacy Policy

## **Effective Date: March 18, 2010**

## **Introduction**

This Privacy Statement describes how Binary Systems collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.binary.com.

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement, please send them to us by email to info@binary.com.

## **For All Visitors to Our Site**

### **Contact Us by Email**

If you submit personal information, such as your email address, we will use that information to respond to your question or request for information. We will not share your information with third parties without your explicit permission.

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that a Web site can place on your computer's hard drive in order to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it easier to use certain site functions. The cookie transmits this information back to the Web site's computer. Many users do not know that cookies are being placed on their computers when they visit Web sites. If you want to know when this happens, or prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a Web site attempts to place a cookie on your computer.

### **Web Site Analytics**

We use a third-party Web analytics service provider that uses cookies, Web beacons, and other Web site technologies to help us analyze both how users use this Web site and the effectiveness of our marketing search terms. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this Web site (including, without limitation, your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by this service provider. They will use this information to evaluate your use of our Web site and compile aggregated reports for us. The information that our service provider collects and provides to us is not personally identifiable.

### **Web Site Surveys**

We use a third-party Web site survey service provider whose privacy practices may differ from those of Binary Systems. If you submit personal information while participating in the survey, your information is subject to their privacy statements. Binary Systems´ Privacy Statement does not apply to information you may submit. We encourage you to read carefully the privacy statement at the start of the survey, or [ **Read Web Site Survey Privacy Policy**](http://4q.iperceptions.com/privacy.aspx "Web Site Survey Privacy Policy") now.

### **Information automatically collected by our site**

Our servers automatically collect certain aggregated, non-personally identifying information--such as your computer's IP address; the number of users clicking on a particular link, service, or advertisement; the type of browser in use; and pages viewed--when you visit our site. We use this information to understand how visitors navigate through our site, to enhance your experience while using our site, and to make the materials we post as valuable to visitors as possible. We do not link this information to personally identifiable information.

### **Links to Other Web Sites**

This Privacy Statement applies to Binary Systems services only. Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Binary Systems. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. Binary Systems´ Privacy Statement does not apply to information you may submit to those sites. We encourage you to read carefully the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

### **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

Please note that this Privacy Statement may change from time to time. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect the personally identifying information we have collected through our site, we will post those changes in this space and advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. We will also post a notice on our home page that this Privacy Statement has changed. Each version of this Privacy Statement will be identified at the top by its effective date.
